sup everyone timbers 1 3 4 5 he was a
very special video today so something
really awesome happened I was at my
local Dollar General and so I don't know
how I maybe it was because of my voice
maybe is because I was beating up a mana
fan but somebody recognized me as him
was one of the five and he gave me a
bunch of rock candy and that he
bought from Dollar Tree I knew a Haley
and so I thought hey I'll go and make a
taste test of these candies that this
random guy gave me there of Mexicans of
candies I never heard of them but I
think that's adds to the fun he told me
I should block I shouldn't eat them
until on screen because well apparently
some of them are good some of them are
really really bad but I think I'll be
the judge of that
the first one we got is salsa Getty
which I think is a mix of sauce and
spaghetti I don't really know what to it
I mean how can this not be good
sauce and spaghetti get the out I'm
gonna love that then our next one
is copper in dough which I guess it's
just fruit stick so comes with
12 these poor dog that's a
CI I mean apparently these with
two fours also oh my way home I got all
this for two bucks oh my God hey
it's cold so yeah I think apparently
this is Loy being right now or
something because eat now googley
apparently it sucks ass but I don't
think it's gonna I can't wait try this
oh my God
oh my what the oh that's music ass
what is that oh my God oh my God it's
exactly what it says it is it's gummy
candy made taste
saw a saw in spaghetti take a penalty it
looks like it comes with my pack or some
don't know what this is I must be
put on top what he's like all coveting
what the I don't know how to
be touching this I got this from some
guy office ready I'm opening this
come on oh my God why is this packed so
hot
who wants to steal this how would
I guess that mean it's doing its job
it's keeping me the out so okay God
open paradise and taste is pop put it on
this can ruin it let me smell that
what the I'm just putting on oh ah
what oh this was like if that just Jaco
bill says what the oh my God oh there's
so much what the oh
oh my God oh I get this is why
expect for Mexico I'm not how about so I
don't call for cookie sheet how am I
supposed to eat this oh my oh oh
how am I supposed to eat this oh my God
does that look good
no I uh oh my God oh it's stinks
oh my God I'm I mean my mixing this
oh
oh no way I suppose we mix it around
first oh
I also separate the noodles plop put the
sauce on now it's a oh my God oh
oh this smells bad yeah that's it free
time good nothing about strike Taco Bell
oh my God Chao anh oh my God - how
it's just - hold on I wanna see this
oh it's talked about oh my God what
this is taco Bell sauce oh my God damn
sorry bad let's not have a head
alright so my laptop I'm filming this
shoe with my laptop
[Music]
now sucks ass I'm not buying
that
how can this not be good luck
just fruit sticks this seems so good oh
my God I'm gonna need this after the
house mom I don't know what the
that was
I might get diarrhea some
Taco Bell season
I got a poop all right are you serious
maybe the soybean meal
Oh No what the what is that
what is that is that malt is that that's
not more visit fruits can multi-campus
[Music]
know this can't be this can't be how
suppose it look like this now boy looks
like on the box
this map involved so Yolo
these are pouch dude I'll Google Apps
I'm done eating this year I put them go
mmm
no babe Oh put this over for this over
that I won't stick down my ass
stick this on my ass I need a damn
that's cool
mmm oh my God
ships on a car what
the do you want mama make a video
no no I got bigger
who the up mom I mean Papa
Reno's no you oh my God damn
hang the up you sorry
about that everyone sums up Siebert just
gotta be stupid so I'm mom I'm almost
coming home I got me I'd all right
go write this up